<resources>

    <string-array name="creatures_list">
        <item >Minotaur</item>
        <item>Meduza</item>
        <item>Centaur</item>
        <item>Pegasus</item>
        <item>Ciclop</item>
        <item>Mermaid</item>
        <item>Cerberus</item>
        <item>Hydra</item>
        <item>Dragon</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="app_name">Creatures of Mythology</string>
<!--    &lt;!&ndash; TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text &ndash;&gt;-->
<!--    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>-->
    <string name="first_Fragment_Body">Here, at Creature of Mythology we want to awaken younger and older generations curiosity towards the history and mythology of
        different ancient civilization. With this app, the veil of mystery that covers the dangers and blessings of the ancient world will dissapear. I
        hope to make the users interested in the stories of the past that used to explain the old world. Use your camera to catch a photo of the
        creature you want to learn more or look around in the library to see more. </string>
    <string name="mino_Body">The minotaur is a monster originated in the Minoan culture in the island of Crete. He is associated with the crete labyrith.
        He was the son of o mortal woman, queen of Crete, and a divine bull send by Poseidon as a gift. He was eating human flesh and the king locked it
        a very complicated labyrinth created by Daidalus. For its food the minoan king demanded a human sacrifice of 14 young Athenians each year. In one
        of such sacrifices was the hero Theseus. The young man, with the help of princess Ariadne, manages to decapited the monster.</string>
    <string name="med_Body">Medusa is one of the tree sisters gorgons and is the only one mortal. Her appearence is of a woman with snake hair and
        lower body of a snake. That is the older version of the story. In a newer version medusa is a mortal woman, who after an adventure with
        Poseidon in Athena\'s temple, was cursed by the goddess with having snake hair and looking in her eyes can petrify anyone. Her head severed still
        had the power to petrify and after the hero Perseus cut her head, used as a weapon. From her severed head 2 creatures appeared, Chrysaor and Pegasus.</string>
    <string name="cen_Body">Centaur were creatures that run through the woods. Having the appearance of a man with lower body of a horse, they were a tribe
    that lived near Tesalia region. After their barbaric behavior at Iapis\'s king, Piritou, wedding there have been many fights between humans and centaur.
    They were a symbol of wild unruly and violent behaviour, the most well known centaur is Chiron, who lacked in this traits and served as mentor figure
        for many heroes.</string>
    <string name="peg_Body">Pegasus is a horse usually depicted withe with wings. One myth says about him that he was born out of Medusa decapited
        head, while others related about his birth that was related to the Athens fundation myth. In which Poseidon and Athena fought to win the
    title of guarding deity. Poseidon offers the pegasus (creared by him) and the chariot and Athena offers the olive tree and knowledge about
    agriculture. </string>
    <string name="cer_Body">Cerberus is the guarding dog from Underworld entrance, greek afterlife. It was pictured as a very big dog with three heads
        and the tail was a fire breathing snake. It\'s the offspring of the Echidna and Typhon. One of the most known aparitions it had
        was in the Labors of Hercules, where the hero was tasked to get Cerberus to a King Eurystheus. Hades agreed to this only if Hercule managed to take
        Cerberus without hurting him. And Hercule lifted it up. </string>
    <string name="hdr_Body">Hydra, or Hydra of Lerna, was a monster that theorize the people near the lake of Lerna. It was another of the children of Echidna
    and Typhon and it had the body of a snake with 9 heads, one of which was immortal. Her breath was toxic and blood a very potent poison and cutting one of her
    heads did nothing since cutting one made 2 more to grow from that place. The monster was slain by Heracles in one of his 12 labours. He used the monster\'s
    blood on the tips of his arrows to make them lethal. One legend has it that the city Baile Herculane was involved in the story, the monuntains around them
    being created in the desperate attends of the monster to flee and the immortal head of the monster being buried underneath the city.</string>
    <string name="drg_Body">The Dragon is one of the oldest symbols of power and wealth and it\'s the ancient creature to be present in different cultures that
    did not communicate with each other. He is slightly different in appearance around the globe, in Asian cultures being more similar with a giant snake with legs that could
    fly while European had the more known image of a big 4 legged creature with wings which often spits fire and gourds treasure. It goes to have many names and
    subspicies but one key aspect remain in all variations, that was to be respected and feared by the humans. </string>
</resources>